[{"answer": "I -- I feel good.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "So how does that make you feel?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "A lot -- a lot of people...", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "How many people do you meet on a daily basis that go, you are my hero?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "You -- all you try to do is just relax, really.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "When you get down on those blocks and you're about to explode, what actually goes through the Golden Bolt's mind?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Well, it's just hard work.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "What does it take to be a champion, not just any old champion, to be a great champion?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "It's everything.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "Is it all of it, do you think?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "For me, uh, Michael Johnson was definitely one.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "-- who are your heroes, sporting heroes?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "And I want to know whether you can basically sing like Marley?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "You've got no game?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "-- I can't really sing.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "I've tried, though, but...", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "Oh, the one -- my one song which I always sing is like...", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "Can you do any Bob Marley for me?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Without a doubt.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "Are you going to -- are you going to go for it in Rio?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Well, I've -- well, I've -- I've mentioned this to my coach and I've said it to him.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "How many -- how many real -- as you sit here now, how many do you think you can race in Rio?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "(INAUDIBLE) yes.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "ORGAN: These are Puma, right?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "Do you wear these?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "That's the key, though.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Huh?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "World Junior Championships, 2002.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "If you had five minutes to live and I had the power to relive a moment for you from your life, what would you choose?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "It was -- it was one of my -- it was a life-changing experience for me in every sense.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "Why that?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "Once?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "Vice versa.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "Did she break your heart?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "We both -- we both had our problems.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "Oh, really?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "Yes, I think it's a massive blessing.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "How does it feel to be an inspiration for literally people who are disabled the entire world over, as you are now, thanks to the Olympics?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Oh, actually, I met him at the Paralympics, and I watched that -- your interview with him and -- and I had a long chat with him.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "It's like of all the things to choose, why that?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "She was just crying.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "What did she say to you?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "I'm actually really good friends with Michael.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "And do you understand that argument?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "No, it is definitely a debate that needed to be brought up.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "So as you -- now you've had time to calm down and reflect on it, what do you think?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Yes, we're going to -- that's the plan.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Are you going to run in Rio?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "I haven't had much time to think about that.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "-- since your Olympic appearances?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "Well, I believe the answer is education and I believe if we can find a way to get the kids to communicate -- and, seriously, arm them with education, then I think they can make the correct choices.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "What is the answer?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "You know, I ask the same question.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "What is behind this?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "HOMAS: You know, I'm a kid that grew up in poverty, so I understand that, you know, there -- you thirst and you want acknowledgement and power.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "What is it about the gun that is so appealing to these young gang members in Chicago?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "Respect, power.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "And respect?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "You know, I am so glad that I didn't have anything to do with that deal --", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "Would you have let him go, if you were -- if you'd still been the Knicks coach?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "You know, with such a direct question, I think it deserves a direct answer.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "Would you have sold or allowed them to sell Jeremy Lin if he was playing for you at the time?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "Well, you know, you never say never.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "Any plans to come back one day?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "So the door is open?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "I like it.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "And the Nets moving to Brooklyn?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "I like it.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "You did?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "I'm doing great.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "Mike, how are you?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "You think he's done a good enough job to deserve being re-elected?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "We have to have some Republican representative and he has to tell you.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "Why are the Republicans so out of touch?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "Health care.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "When you go back to your old streets and you meet your old guys and so on, what do you think the real cares and fears of the average American on the street are right now?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "Real happiness from my perspective, I can only tell you -- as you're asking me, from my ordeals in life and challenges.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "Where is real happiness throughout that process?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "You know, I wanted Lindsey to win so bad.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "What advice could you give somebody like that?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "She needs a good support system.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "What does she need to do, Mike, to get out of it?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "I've met her, yes.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 647, "question": "Have you met her before?", "qSentId": 646}, {"answer": "I think she's an awesome person that's just got to get it together.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "What do you think of her?", "qSentId": 648}, {"answer": "I have at least a hundred at my house now, yes.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 690, "question": "Do you still keep pigeons?", "qSentId": 689}, {"answer": "Yes, that's what I do.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 692, "question": "You love them, don't you?", "qSentId": 691}, {"answer": "I can' tell you.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 694, "question": "What is it about the pigeon?", "qSentId": 693}, {"answer": "I feel like I'm in heaven.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 697, "question": "When you're with them, what do you feel?", "qSentId": 696}, {"answer": "Always.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 704, "question": "You have always been like that with them?", "qSentId": 703}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 742, "question": "When you hear him talk about what you did to him and for his life, what do you feel?", "qSentId": 741}, {"answer": "Listen, I don't know if someone needs someone like Cus.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 751, "question": "Does everybody need somebody like a Cus D'Amato to just get a grip of them?", "qSentId": 750}, {"answer": "We're going to go all over, 36 cities across the nation.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 763, "question": "What are you going to do with it next?", "qSentId": 762}, {"answer": "The city I did my time in and stuff.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 768, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 767}, {"answer": "That's going to be pretty awesome.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 770, "question": "How will that feel?", "qSentId": 769}, {"answer": "Last time I got my ass kicked.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 786, "question": "When was the last time you put on a pair of boxing gloves?", "qSentId": 785}, {"answer": "Knocking out is not necessarily having a hard punch.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 791, "question": "If I was to really want to knock somebody out, what is the absolutely best way to do it?", "qSentId": 790}, {"answer": "I don't know, you jab.", "docId": "121201pmt", "aSentId": 795, "question": "How do you hide it?", "qSentId": 794}]